(Penny:)I did?
(Sheldon:)The photo of the cat
who wants to "Has Cheezburger?"
(Penny:)Oh, come on, everybody loves Lolcats.
(Penny:)They're cute and they can't spell...
...because they're cats.
(Sheldon:)I trusted you with my e-mail address
and you betrayed that trust...
(Sheldon:)...by sending me Internet banality.
Strike one.
(Sheldon:)Touching my food, strike two.
(Leonard:)Don't worry,
they only stay on your record for a year.
(Howard:)You can get them removed early
but you have to take his class.
- Oh, come on, I touched one onion ring.
- And then you put it back.
(Sheldon:)Compromising the integrity
of all the other onion rings.
(Penny:)Oh, honey, the buses don't go
where you live, do they?
Look, I wish I could be more lenient
with you.
(Sheldon:)But since you've become
a permanent member...
...I've to hold you to the same standards
as everybody else.
(Leonard:)Congratulations,
you're officially one of us.